I've heard a lot of people on YouTube
talking about how now that AI
is becoming a
big thing,
just having a course as information by
itself is not going to be as
valuable. Having a community
and having a Discord or a cohort
is going to be more
and more important.
Very good question. AI, I don't think
is as good as you think it is.
Not yet. It could be in a few years,
but also imagine you said,
"I want to get in
shape," and AI said,
"I need you to exercise, do this,
this." You just don't listen
to it. And this is the beauty of it.
Someone spends 2,000 hours on a call with
you.
That money is wasted unless they do all
the things you talk about.
When you tell them to build an email list,
let's say.
Someone pays me $1,000 to go, "Do that."
If they do it, it's worth the money.
If they don't do it, it isn't.
So when people pay AI or don't pay AI
or get AI to do it for free,
they just won't
actually execute it.
The fact of the matter
is they need to pay someone to do it.
We've all got injuries we know how to fix,
but we pay a physio, so we do it